Paris.
With all its monuments.
its department stores.
its fancy bars...
It's the city of light. The city of love.
The whole city's a postcard.
But Paris is also the city of crime.
Thefts. robberies. murders. prostitution.
Six mafia families run
their businesses in this city.
and none of them
tolerate anarchy or chaos.
But when money and power are at stake.
chaos is inevitable.
Even in organized crime. someone
needs to keep order among the mobsters.
The underworld has a sheriff:
The Fury.
She intervenes when a crime
is committed amongst criminals.
And those who have met her
are no longer alive to tell the tale.
Except for me.
TODAY
My name is Lyna.
I'm just an average college student.
Shh! Hang on! It's...
That guy being loud and singing
out of tune? That's Elie. my boyfriend.
MOM - HAPPY BIRTHDAY. DARLING.
COMING TOMORROW? WE WANT TO SEE YOU.
Your folks?
Mm-mm.
- Is it your lover?
- Well. of course it is.
You put on the same face
when it's your parents.
Here.
They throwing a party for you?
I could finally meet them. right?
- What's wrong with the damn door?
- No. you're right.
There's no rush anyway.
Whenever you're ready.
It's only been three years. after all.
My parents. it's complicated.
I don't wanna complicate things for us.
E... ver.
My parents are criminals
and Elie's a cop.
So you can see
why I don't want them to meet.
I'm sorry.
Stupid idiots.
Wrong apartment.
Why didn't you say anything?
It's complicated to stop you.
Didn't you have class this morning?
Damn it. the alarm didn't go off!
Damn it. damn it. damn it! Damn it!
I don't know what to say.
Try "damn it."
- Out of clean clothes. baby?
- Yep.
I've been wearing this for a couple days.
Could be worse.
Ever since I was a little girl.
my favorite day has been my birthday.
My parents used to throw these
huge parties for me. Crazy parties.
Hey.
No.
Here. try this.
Oh. thanks.
Birthdays with Elie are different.
They're smaller. more intimate.
Definitely better.
Did you know you're magnificent?
And did you know that I love you?
Oh! Uh. hold on. brush your teeth.
Brush your teeth.
- No. yeah. yeah. no. no. It's bad.
- Oh no. No. oh I love you!
Keep your distance. ma'am. please.
It should've been
the case again this year.
- Come on. stop.
- Mmmm. Mm.
It's actually gonna be
the worst birthday of my life.
Don't come home early tonight. okay?
Give me some time to prepare your party.
Mm-hmm.
It'll be epic.
BANKER
INCOMING CALL
Mr. Laroche.
Yeah. I... I know I'm redefining
the meaning of a bank overdraft.
but don't freeze my account. just...
What?
YOUR BANK - TRANSFER
€ 2.550.857
My father is the Parisian
underworld's accountant.
He moves. launders
and redistributes money.
He's unseen. and unknown.
When I was a kid. I noticed
gangsters were always at our house.
I didn't know why they came.
but one day. I finally understood.
That's why I distanced myself
from my parents.
- Hi. little darling.
- Hi. Mom.
- Happy birthday. sweetie.
- Thanks.
Mwah. Mwah.
- Your old man will be happy to see you.
- Well. won't be for long.
Two million. Papa?
Come on. who gives two million
as a birthday gift? No one.
I mean. it could be because. uh.
people don't love their kids enough.
Don't worry.
the money's origin is untraceable.
Your father knows what he's doing.
He's the best. The boss.
I already told you
I don't want your money. I'm not like you.
Having all that money
in my account is too dangerous.
I'll make it disappear.
But you know.
an old man like me.
not being able to look after his daughter.
that's really rough. you know?
Mm. Papa.
Okay but. the boss
should never sign his transfers.
You'll get caught for that someday.
The last six digits
of your bank transfer.
THE BOSS
Seriously?
All I've ever wanted
was a normal life.
But when you're born into the underworld.
sooner or later. it catches up with you.
Stay here!
No. no. no. no.
- No!
- I love you.
No! Mama!
Mama!
Police!
"Are you okay?" "Are you hurt. ma'am?"
You expect me to believe
you didn't know
about your parents' business?
Hey!
All of your father's documents
are encrypted.
But you know how to decode them. right?
My mother. is she. uh...
She's alive.
but we're talking about you here.
Don't be their scapegoat.
'Cause believe me.
girls like you don't do well in prison.
Just with what you have in your account.
I can put you on remand for six months.
I wanna help you.
So just tell me who shot your father.
I'm sure you saw something.
Your father took one bullet
in the eye and one in the hand.
That's not your average hit.
That's a message signed by The Fury.
Wait. what?
Lyna! Lyna!
What happened?
Hey. You okay. baby? You okay?
- Mm-hm.
- The hell are you doing here?
- She shouldn't be here. she's a victim.
- Okay. hey. stop it! Francis?
Don't touch me.
I said. don't touch me!
- Damn it. let go of me!
- Calm down.
- Get off me! Lyna. I'll be back.
- Step back!
- Get off me. Lyna! Get off me!
- Come on.
Get your hands off me. Lyna!
You're the closest
I've ever gotten to The Fury.
So. you better give me a good description
or I'll make your life a living hell.
When I was little. my father
taught me to play chess. mahjong. and go.
My mother. on the other hand.
put me in the ring.
"If you learn how to box.
you'll be ready to face the world.
my sweet girl."
Sorry. Mom.
but I guess I'm still not ready.
I was terrible at boxing.
I got my ass kicked.
At least I knew how to take a punch.
Learning how to strike takes time.
And in here. time's all I got.
- You've got a visitor.
- Tell 'em I'm busy. okay?
You don't have a choice. it's a cop.
Elie. I told you. I don't want you
to see me here. not like th...
So. sweetheart. did this month here
help you remember?
I have nothing to say.
I don't know anything.
- I'm a nobody.
- Oh no.
The shooter was a pro.
your father gets killed.
your mother sent to the hospital.
and you... nothing?
- Not even a scratch?
- What do you know?
Uh. I don't know anything. I just...
I just state what the facts are.
Then I try to understand.
All the other cops?
They don't care about The Fury.
Nor this case.
they think The Fury's a myth.
And that your father was a thug
who got what he deserved.
"He's better off dead.
his murder was a favor to the world."
- So you won't do anything?
- No.
The investigation's closed.
Game over. It's official.
I'm the last
to still have a little interest in it.
But hey.
if you've got nothing to tell me. then...
Does The Fury mean anything to you?
Want some advice?
Don't ever mention that name.
To anybody.
I'm not looking for advice.
I want answers.
My father never hurt a single person.
He doesn't deserve this.
I think I feel tear rolling down my face.
Oh. no.
If you're not doing anything.
I'll bring The Fury to you.
I look forward to that.
5 MONTHS LATER
My father was murdered.
and I wanna know why.
You transferred here yesterday.
you weren't alone.
The Shark?
Is that who you're interested in?
They put her in solitary confinement.
Every time she's transferred.
she eats someone's ear
as soon as she arrives.
To show 'em who she is.
As for me.
I don't know if I'll fit in here.
Nah. you'll be fine.
You have to watch out for three things.
The inmates.
the food
and that guard there.
So. be polite. avoid the expired pasta.
and as for him.
I'll show you.
So. Lyna. last day?
You're gonna miss me. right?
Well done. champ. You'll spend
your final hours here in solitary.
They don't care much about you
to lock you up with me.
Did the bosses send you to break me?
No.
- Who do you work for?
- Nobody.
I'm just looking for answers.
The underworld sheriff. the investigator.
the magistrate. The Fury...
Don't say that name.
Why?
Scared they'll come here?
Damn it.
When I got here.
I didn't know how to fight.
I'd never even been hit. imagine that?
Then I found this at the library.
- Self-defense in 16 lessons.
- You can't learn that from books.
Yeah. sure. but it hurts all the same.
In six months. you're the first big shot
I've seen from the underworld.
So you're gonna tell me
all you know about The Fury.
Sorry. excuse me. Sorry. sorry.
Sorry. excuse me. sorry.
Sorry. Lyna?
TO: ELIE
US TWO. SOON. PROMISE.
Mom?
My little darling. How are you?
Mom.
I've missed you so much.
Mrs. Guerrab?
Shall we go in?
My little darling. how are you?
She'll get better.
but it'll take time.
A consequence of the medically-induced
coma your mother was placed in
for the treatment of her injuries.
She recognized me. right?
Sometimes. amnesic patients
subconsciously come up with mechanisms
to give that impression.
But it can only do her good to see you.
My little darling.
How are you?
Not great.
Not great at all.
And I can't tell anyone about it.
Elie...
I'd just put him in danger. and...
and I don't even think
he'd get what I'm doing.
Prison was just horrible.
I got my ass kicked. Mama.
Every day.
But I got back up.
That's what you told me to do. didn't you?
I'm gonna find out who did this to Papa.
And don't worry. I know how
to force them to come out.
Because I figured something out.
The trick to getting to The Fury
is to follow the money.
What'll be your stake today?
We've got one joker.
You have to follow the ace of clubs.
It's very simple.
Good. The ace of clubs. ace of clubs.
Yeah. the ace. you're welcome.
I came out with 500 euros.
I only have 300 left. It's your turn now.
If you have the cash.
you just might win. right?
Today's your lucky day. One. two. three.
Place your bets. It's your lucky day.
Unfortunately. ma'am. you lost. Ah...
You won't draw out The Fury
by hitting the guys at the bottom.
You gotta go higher in the chain.
Hey. what's up?
- Any chance I can bet on tonight's game?
- Get lost.
Hi.
Uh. a couple of those. please?
Ahh. sorry. they've expired.
That's too bad. I was hoping
to find a golden ticket in the wrapper.
She's out of jail.
And she's looking for you.
Okay.
You keep watching her.
And let me know when she's getting close.
Hi. guys.
What a day!
Who would suspect
that there's a secret casino
under one of the biggest
tourist attractions in Paris?
Getting in was easy.
I put on a nice smile.
slipped some cash to the bouncer...
Getting out will be harder
because from here on in.
everyone around me is a criminal.
Blackjack. fold.
Place your bets. gentlemen.
I thought I'd found
the perfect spot for observing.
Discreet and safe.
Are you betting?
I was wrong.
Here is your hammer.
In this world. all games are dangerous.
Rien ne va plus.
- Hammer on the table.
- Oh.
- Oh. he got the hammer.
- Sir. you know the rule.
Ma'am.
Uh. I'm gonna fold.
Nineteen.
The gentleman leads with 20.
I'm sorry.
About what?
You're just winning at a card game. right?
Bank error.
Ma'am.
There are six hammer cards in the deck.
I'm afraid the odds aren't in your favor.
- Hey. hey. hey. hey!
- Stop that!
Whoa. whoa. whoa!
Where do you think you're going?
- Thanks.
- Wait. wait.
This was your card. You won.
No. no. no. You don't understand.
I always win.
Always.
- Um. okay? I have to go now.
- Yeah. Yeah. sure.
But not until you tell me who you are.
- Who do you work for?
- I don't work for anyone!
Hey. my name's Orso. in case...
Apparently she's in a bit of a rush.
Yeah. boss.
She knows about the casino money.
She saw the garbage truck.
she's up to something.
No. No. no. no. not now.
She's gonna need some preparation.
She'll go see her mother now.
You'll only get in if you break a window.
Get in the car before
you do something stupid.
246 texts. Elie? Really?
When I'm worried about you.
I get a little crazy. I'm sorry.
I'm okay.
Did you wait for me all day?
No. no. no.
- I forgot I can't hide anything from you.
- And I forgot that you're so messy.
A cop and a convict.
what will your colleagues think?
That sounds like a porno.
so they'll love it for sure.
Why did you stop?
I know I promised you an epic birthday.
I did my best.
GIVE ME 48 HOURS AND WE'LL START OVER?
I have a plan to draw out The Fury.
but it involves stealing
a heavily guarded truck full of money.
I know. doesn't sound like a great idea.
But this truck is my only chance.
ID please?
Damn it!
Who the fuck are you?
With that large jacket and your piercings?
Did you forget?
Cops never do inspections alone.
Stop!
Come on. let's go. let's go.
Hey!
All the money's here.
Nothing's missing. I don't get it.
Why would they steal the truck
and leave the cash?
Who are these lunatics?
Whoever he is. he's clever.
He spotted our route.
hijacked our truck
and abandoned it in the middle of Paris.
Huh.
But didn't bother
to get our GPS tracker removed?
That doesn't make sense.
- You know what he wanted?
- What?
He didn't want the truck or the money.
He wanted me.
He did all this
just to bring me to this exact spot.
And he's watching us now.
Yeah.
I got ya.
You get down right now.
Come on. Right now.
But where's my toy car?
I don't know. you must've
dropped it somewhere. Look for it.
- Damn!
- Oh. I'm sorry. Excuse me.
Are you a photographer?
Looks nice. right?
Would you like a cookie?
Thanks.
My husband makes them.
They're gluten free.
What's up? Did you find it?
- No.
- Come on. help me look.
He must have left tracks.
Never mind. I've got it.
So. what are you doing here?
Watch what you say.
I think we're being listened to.
Copy.
You okay?
Yeah. yeah.
I can see ya.
Damn it.
- Stop her. guys.
- Hey. hold on a second.
How did you find me so quickly?
Watch what you say.
I think we're being listened to.
So you're The Fury.
It ain't cookies
I got for you. believe me.
Forget your gun. okay?
Your customer from Pont Neuf.
take me to her place.
BLACK BELT CERTIFICATE
(YOU SAID 48 HOURS? I'M READY:)
Damn it!
Gotta put your phone on silent
when sneaking into someone's home.
But you did great apart from that.
You got further than anyone else.
Good job.
Stealing the truck was really smart.
You're bright.
- And you're careless. aren't you?
- No. but I'm married.
He's a messy DIYer. you know?
I ask him to tidy up. but well...
On the other hand.
sawdust is pretty great.
It soaks up blood.
Why did you kill my father?
Oh. that's why you found me. then?
Well. found. or. uh.
looked for me. right?
I'm the one who led you here.
do you realize that?
No. I've never said anything
about The Fury.
To anybody. Ever.
I swear to you.
But her...
You'll tell her everything
she wants to know.
And don't make things too easy for her.
Don't feel bad. though.
I'm always one step ahead.
It's a gift and it's my job.
Well. your fighting skills need some work.
But I think there's some potential.
We'll make something of it.
If you work for me.
I don't work for anyone!
Selma?
Selma? Did you find the bott...
This is the new girl. Lyna Guerrab.
Lyna. my husband. Papou.
Oh. Nice to meet you.
- Your wine.
- Hm? Oh!
So. uh...
- On your head.
- Hm?
On your head.
She sees everything.
So...
Well. I think this is great. It's...
It's perfect. Are you staying for dinner?
No.
Ah.
Well. another time. then.
See you later.
So tell me. did you get the answers
you were looking for?
Do you get that your father
embezzled The Godfathers' money?
Oh. What are you gonna do with that?
That's not true. he would never do that.
If you'd looked in the right place
you wouldn't have...
Either shoot or ramble about your life.
I didn't kill your father.
And I don't have to lie to you
because now you know who I am.
- And you're already done for anyway.
- Wait. wait!
He left a message.
What message?
Shit. I'm having trouble articulating
with a gun on my face.
Okay. okay.
Three. three. seven. three. nine.
JELLY
The last numbers of his bank transfer.
It was a game between us.
What the hell is the "jelly"?
The nickname of one of The Godfathers.
Did he force my father
to embezzle the money and then kill him?
If he did. there will be war.
I gotta talk to him then.
I don't think you grasp
the complexity of this mess.
Take your time before answering.
Who do you work for?
You okay. boss?
Lyna. Mud Man. The Fixer.
The hell is she doing here?
I work for her.
FURIES